Emanuel Ruben Piore Papers ca.1918-1986 Mss.Ms.Coll.80
American Philosophical Society
- Series V. Photographs, ca. 1918-1982; 6 boxes; 1 linear foot (Box Series V: 1-6)
  - Piore, Emanuel Ruben, 1908-2000 -- Unidentified conference, n.d.; 1 item
    Group photograph taken inside
  - Piore, Emanuel Ruben, 1908-2000 -- Unidentified conference, n.d.; 1 item
    Group photograph taken inside dining room
  - Piore, Emanuel Ruben, 1908-2000 -- Unidentified conference, n.d.; 1 item
    Group photograph taken in front of map.
  - Piore, Emanuel Ruben, 1908-2000 -- Unidentified conference, n.d.; 1 item
    Group photograph.
  - Piore, Emanuel Ruben, 1908-2000 -- Unidentified conference, n.d.; 1 item
    Group photograph, color.
  - Piore, Emanuel Ruben, 1908-2000 -- Unidentified conference, n.d.; 1 item
    Group photograph, seven seated, seven standing.
  - Piore, Emanuel Ruben, 1908-2000 -- Unidentified Dinner, n.d.; 1 item
    Piore, Dr. Trytten and unidentified man, seated at table
  - Piore, Emanuel Ruben, 1908-2000 -- Unidentified Dinner, n.d.; 1 item
    Piore and two unidentified men seated at table
  - Piore, Emanuel Ruben, 1908-2000 -- Unidentifed, miscellaneous, n.d.; 1 item
    Piore and unidentified man standing outside in front of tree.
  - Piore, Emanuel Ruben, 1908-2000 -- Unidentifed, miscellaneous, n.d.; 2 items
    Piore and several other unidentified men arriving at airport.
  - Piore, Emanuel Ruben, 1908-2000 -- Unidentifed, miscellaneous, n.d.; 3 items
    Piore and two unidentified men at construction site?
  - Piore, Emanuel Ruben, 1908-2000 -- Unidentifed party, n.d.; 1 item
    Piore and unidentified man standing at party.
  - Piore, Emanuel Ruben, 1908-2000 -- Unidentifed party?, n.d.; 1 item
    Piore and two unidentified men standing at party.
  - Piore, Emanuel Ruben, 1908-2000 -- Unidentifed Party, n.d.; 3 items
    Piore and unidentified man standing at party. Piore and one unidentified woman and one man seated.
  - Piore, Emanuel Ruben, 1908-2000 -- Unidentifed Party, n.d.; 1 item
    Piore with four unidentified men standing at party.
  - Piore, Emanuel Ruben, 1908-2000 -- Unidentifed speech, n.d.; 1 item
    Piore standing at podium.
  - Piore, Emanuel Ruben, 1908-2000 -- Unidentified woman and Emanuel Piore seated outside on steps, [ca. 1928]; 1 item
  - Piore, Margot, 1942- ? -- Informal portrait, n.d.; 1 item
  - Piore, Michael J., [ca. 1940]; 1 item
    Michael Piore standing holding two pipes.
  - Piore, Michael J., [ca. 1942]; 1 item
    Michael Piore seated in chair. Christmas card.
  - Piore, Michael J., [ca. 1946]; 1 item
    Michael Piore standing on dock.
  - Piore, Michael J., [ca. 1955]; 1 item
  - Piore, Michael J., Margo Piore and Jane Piore, [ca. 1946]; 9 items
  - Piore, Michael J., Margo Piore and Jane Piore, [ca. 1948]; 2 items
  - Piore, Nora, n.d.; 1 item
    Nora Piore, seated, reading.
  - Piore, Nora -- Informal portrait, n.d.; 1 item
    Nora Piore, holding glasses.
  - Piore, Nora -- Nora Piore with baby, n.d.; 1 item
  - Piore, Nora -- Nora and Michael Piore, [ca. 1940]; 1 item
    Nora and Michael Piore standing outside.
  - Piore, Nora -- Studio portrait, n.d.; 7 items
  - Piore, Olga -- Mrs. Flynn and Olga Piore, 1948; 1 item
    Olga Piore and Mrs. Flynn standing outside.
  - Piore, Olga -- Friend of, 1 item
    Unidentified man, studio portrait.
  - Piore,Olga -- Tannersville, New York, n.d.; 2 items
    Olga with friends.
  - Rees, Mina Spiegel, 1902-, n.d.; 1 item
    Rees, informal, seated a desk.
  - Romanoff, Michael, n.d.; 1 item
    Romanoff, head and shoulders, smoking pipe.
  - Rotor-craft portable helicopter, [ca. 1950-1960]; 1 item
  - Russotto, Carol and Henrietta, 1 item
    Standing in front of store window.
  - Sayre, David, 1974 March; 2 items
    Removed from Series II; General, folder 17
  - Senior Naval Scientists -- Meeting, Naval Underwater Ordnance Station, 1954 April 22-23; 1 item
  - Society of Research Founders of the Hebrew University of Jerusalem, 4 items
    Removed from Universitah ha-Ivrit bi-Yerushalayim, folder 1
  - Tamiment dining room, n.d.; 1 item
  - Uga [?] -- Piore's uncle, n.d.; 1 item
    Studio portrait
  - United States Math Olympiad, first -- Opening Cermony, 1972; 1 item
    Removed from Series I; State University of New York.
  - United States Underwater Sound Laboratory, 1 item
    Group photograph
  - Woods Hole Oceanographic Institution -- Annual Meeting, 1973 June 21; 1 item
  - Woods Hole Oceanographic Institution -- Annual Meeting, 1974 June 20; 1 item
  - Woods Hole Oceanographic Institution -- Annual Meeting, 1977 June 23; 1 item
    Removed from Series I; American Physical Society, folder 3.
  - Woods Hole Oceanographic Institution -- Annual Meeting, 1979 June 21; 1 item
  - Woods Hole Oceanographic Institution -- Annual Meeting, 1981 June 19; 1 item
  - Woods Hole Oceanographic Institution -- Annual Meeting, 1982 June 18; 1 item
  - World ORT Union, 1984 October; 1 item
    Removed from Series I; World ORT Union, folder 2.
  - Zuras -- Family portrait, n.d.; 1 item
    housed in oversized, 11 x 14 box.
  - Unidentified baby -- negative, n.d.; 1 item
  - Unidentified -- Baby in carriage, n.d.; 4 items
  - Unidentified -- Girls riding bikes, n.d.; 1 item
  - Unidentified -- Miscellaneous photographs, [ca. 1950-1970]; 6 items
    Informal photographs.
  - Unidentified -- Party, [ca. 1960]; 2 items
  - Unidentified -- Scenic photographs, n.d.; 5 items
  - Unidentified -- Skier, [ca. 1940-1950]; 1 item
  - Unidentified -- Young woman, n.d.; 1 item